A Guide to the John C. Watkins Papers 1979-1999
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series III--Office Files, n.d. 1977-1999
  - Route 895 1995-1996 (Box 73)
  - Russell Keller, n.d. 1995-1998 (Box 73)
  - Safety Belt Use Law 1985, 1987 (Box 73)
  - SB 511 Lambert 1998 (Box 73)
  - SB 600 Spinal Manipulation 1998 (Box 73)
  - SCC Compensation Study 1997 (Box 73)
  - Schools/Costs, n.d. 1990-1991 (Box 73)
  - Security Interests, n.d. 1985-1986 (Box 73)
  - Senate 1993 (Box 73)
  - Senate Bills 1998 (Box 73)
  - Senate Clerk's Office 1999 (Box 73)
  - Senator Lugar, n.d. 1995 (Box 73)
  - Service Districts, n.d. 1987, 19992 (Box 73)
  - Shipyard Op/Ed Article 1998 (Box 73)
  - SJR 261 1998 (Box 73)
  - Social Security 1986, 1991 (Box 73)
  - Soil and Water Conservation 1999 (Box 73)
  - Soil Erosion 1983-1984 (Box 73)
  - Special Session 1 of 2, n.d. 1989 (Box 73)
  - Special Session, 2 of 2, n.d. 1989 (Box 73)
  - Special Session-Roads/Revenues, n.d. 1986-1987 (Box 74)
  - Special Use Permits (HB 2324) 1999 (Box 74)
  - Standards of Learning, n.d. 1995 (Box 74)
  - State Corporation Commission 1986 (Box 74)
  - State Employees 1989-1990 and 1992 (Box 74)
  - State Employees 1998 (Box 74)
  - State Employees 1999 (Box 74)
  - State Government Privatization 1994 (Box 74)
  - State Republican Party, n.d. 1985-1993 (Box 74)
  - State Soil 1998 (Box 74)
  - State Song Proposals 1997-1998 (Box 74)
  - Storm Warnings 1998 (Box 74)
  - State Water Control Board 1983-1985 (Box 74)
  - Students 1998 (Box 74)
  - Students 1999 (Box 74)
  - Study APF/Impact, n.d. 1991 (Box 74)
  - Sullivan Case 1986-1987 (Box 74)
  - Sunday Hunting 1990 (Box 74)
  - Sycamore Mews 1993 (Box 74)
  - Taxation 1958, 1983-1991 (Box 74)
  - Taxes 1998 (Box 74)
  - Thank You Correspondence 1998 (Box 74)
  - Thank You Notes, n.d. 1998 (Box 74)
  - Thank You 1999 (Box 74)
  - Tobacco Settlement 1998 (Box 74)
  - Toll Road Bill-Senate Bill 304 1983-1984, 1990 (Box 74)
  - Tolls 1997-1998 (Box 74)
  - Tom Bliley 1984, 1986 (Box 74)
  - Transfer of Development Rights, n.d. 1978, 1985, 1988-1989 (Box 74)
  - Transfer of Development Rights 1990-1991 (Box 74)
  - Transportation 1999 (Box 74)
  - Transportation 21st Century(SB 79) 1982, 1985-1987 (Box 74)
  - Transportation: 21st Century Phase II 1987 (Box 74)
  - Transportation Districts, n.d. 1989-1994 (Box 74)
  - Trash Correspondence 1998-1999 (Box 74)
  - Trash Waste 1998-1999 (Box 74)
  - Treasury Board Meeting 1983 (Box 74)
  - Trigon 1999 (Box 74)
  - Tuition Assistance Grant Program 1998 (Box 74)
  - 21-day Rule 1999 (Box 74)
  - 288-76 Interchange, n.d. 1986, 1991-1993 (Box 74)
  - Unemployment Trust Fund 1998 (Box 74)
  - UNOS/United Network for Organ Sharing 1994 (Box 74)
  - VCU/MCV 1983-1987 (Box 75)
  - Vepco/Dominion Resources, n.d. (Box 75)
  - Vested Rights (HB 570) 1998 (Box 75)
  - Veto Session, n.d. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Veto Session 1996 (Box 75)
  - Virginia Employees 1977, 1988-1991 (Box 75)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, n.d. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Virginia Institute of Government 1994-1997 (Box 75)
  - Virginia is for Lovers Logo Recommendation 1998 (Box 75)
  - Virginia Prepaid Education 1999 (Box 75)
  - Virginia Tech Agricultural Alumni Organization 1984, 1987 (Box 75)
  - Virginia Tech Athletics 1997 (Box 75)
  - Virginia Tech Land Swap 1985-1987 (Box 75)
  - VMI Case 1991-1993 (Box 75)
  - VMI State Cadetship, n.d. 1997 (Box 75)
  - Volunteer Firefighters and Rescue Squad Pension Fund (HB 437) 1998 (Box 75)
  - VPI Agricultural Alumni Board of Directors, n.d. 1981-1987 (Box 75)
  - Warner, John 1984 (Box 75)
  - Waste Regulations 1997 (Box 75)
  - Water Law (HB 488) 1992 (Box 75)
  - Water Permit Fee Increases 1998 (Box 75)
  - Water Resources Task Force 1990 (Box 75)
  - Water Transfer Corps of Engineers 1984-1987 (Box 75)
  - Western Transportation Corridor (SB 628), n.d. 1997-1998 (Box 75)
  - Wetlands Mitigation Banks (SB 582) 1999 (Box 75)
  - Workers Compensation Insurance 1985, 1992 (Box 75)
  - Y2K (SB 983 and SB 1180) 1999 (Box 75)
  - Y2K Bug 1999 (Box 75)
  - Year Round Schools, n.d. 1990-1991 (Box 75)
- Series IV-Office Files, n.d. 1997-2001
  - 4 for Life, n.d. (Box 76)
  - 9-1-1 Tax Rates, n.d. (Box 76)
  - 21 Day Rule 2000 (Box 76)
  - 21 Day Rule HB 1311, n.d. (Box 76)
  - 288 Lambert Associates Marketing Commonwealth Transportation board 1996-1997 (Box 76)
  - Budget Maps 1999 (Box 76)
  - Correspondence 2000 (Box 76)
  - Issues 2000 (Box 76)
  - Session Miscellaneous 2000 (Box 76)
  - Abortion, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Abortion 2000 (Box 76)
  - Accreditation Council for Graduate Medical Education 1998 (Box 76)
  - Agriculture, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Agriculture 2000 (Box 76)
  - Agency Director Compensation 1999 (Box 76)
  - Agribusiness Council Award (Virginia), n.d. (Box 76)
  - Agriculture, Conservation and National Resources, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Agriculture Issues 2001 (Box 76)
  - Agriculture Subcommittee, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Airport 2000 (Box 76)
  - Appellate Court 2000 (Box 76)
  - Arresting Officer, Duty of, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Attorney General Opinion/Scope Practices 1999 (Box 76)
  - Automobile Dealers Legislation 2000 (Box 76)
  - Bill Tracking Session 2000 (Box 76)
  - Bond Rating-Bond Debt, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Bon Air Juvenile Center, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Budget Information 2000 (Box 76)
  - Budget Revenue Data, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Budget Correspondence 2000 (Box 76)
  - Building Code Violation, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Bus No Response, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Calls Re: Petroleum Products, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Capital Region Caucus, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Caregivers Grant Program 2001 (Box 76)
  - Certificate of Public Nee Law, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Certificate of Public Nee Law 2000 (Box 76)
  - Charlotte, NC, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel 2000 (Box 76)
  - Chesterfield 1999 (Box 76)
  - Chesterfield 2000 (Box 76)
  - Chesterfield Issues 2000 (Box 76)
  - Chesterfield County 2001 (Box 76)
  - Chesterfield Legislative Program 2000 (Box 76)
  - Children's Health 1999 (Box 76)
  - Children's Health Insurance, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Comcast Cable 1999 (Box 76)
  - Combs/Zoning, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Commission on the Future of Transportation in Virginia 1998 (Box 77)
  - Commonwealth Competition Council, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Commonwealth Competition Budget Amendment, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Communication Towers, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Conference Committee-HB 1214 Solicitation Contributions 2000 (Box 77)
  - Congratulations 2000 (Box 77)
  - Congress 2000 (Box 77)
  - Conference Committee SB 34 License Plates 2000 (Box 77)
  - Confidential 1997 (Box 77)
  - Conservation Score for Watkins, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Constituents Requests for Assistance 2000 (Box 77)
  - Consumer Privacy SB 602-The Virginia Consumers' Financial Privacy Protection Act, n.d. (Box 77)
  - CSO Funding, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Dentistry Amendment #1 Senate Bill 806, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Dentistry Amendment #2 Senate Bill 806, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Dentistry Amendment-Amendment for Joint Board Oversight of Practice Expansion, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Dentistry Amendment-Cosmetic Surgery Training Program-Advertisement, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Dentistry Amendment-Naimtu-Office Pictures and Materials, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Dentistry Amendment-Niamtu Warning from AAOMS, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Dentistry Amendment-Oral Surgery Highbred Medicine and Dentistry, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Dentistry Amendment-Procedures Challenged by Litigation, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Dentistry Amendment-Senate Floor Amendments, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Department of Environmental Quality/Ozone 2000 (Box 77)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Disclosure in Land Procedures SB 655, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Divorce No Fault/Minor Children 2000 (Box 77)
  - Draft Report: Powhite Toll Advisory Committee 1997 (Box 77)
  - Eagle Scout 2000 (Box 77)
  - Education 2000 (Box 77)
  - Educational Opportunity Act 2000 (Box 77)
  - Education Tuition Tax Credit 2000 (Box 77)
  - Electric Vehicle 2000 (Box 77)
  - Elementary Counselors SB 164 and HB 245, n.d. (Box 77)
  - E-mail Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 77)
  - Executive Summary Impacts of Transportation on the Greater Richmond Region 1997 (Box 77)
  - Enterprise Zone, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Environment 2001 (Box 77)
  - Environmental, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Family Foundation, n.d. (Box 77)
  - The Family Foundation, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Fenchuk, Gary W., n.d. (Box 77)
  - Firearms, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Firefighters, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Fire/Rescue 1999 (Box 77)
  - Flags 2000 (Box 77)
  - Friends of Regional Service 2000 Greater Richmond Chamber of Commerce 2000 (Box 77)
  - Federal 2000 (Box 77)
  - Greater Enterprises: Brenda Ingram 2001 (Box 77)
  - Gas Deregulation, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Gay and Lesbian Issues 2000 (Box 77)
  - General Correspondence 2000, 6 folders (Box 77)
  - Geographic Information Systems, n.d. (Box 77)
  - George Allen for Senate, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Girl Scouts Gold Award, n.d. (Box 77)
  - Golf Tournament Stonehenge Country Club Richmond, Va 6-12-2000 (Box 77)
  - Governor Gillmore 2000 (Box 77)
  - Governor Gillmore: Substance Abuse Reduction Effort (SABRE) 1999 (Box 77)
  - Governor's Highway/Transportation Funding Proposal 2000 (Box 77)
  - Governor's Speech 1999 (Box 77)
  - Greater Richmond Area Regionalism 1998 (Box 77)
  - Greater Richmond Transit Company 2000 (Box 77)
  - GRTC Bus Line Expansion 1999 (Box 77)
  - GRTC Transportation Study 1999 (Box 77)
  - Greater Richmond Chamber of Commerce 2000 (Box 77)
  - Grove Shaft Park, n.d. (Box 77)
  - HB 1088 1995, 4 folders (Box 78)
  - Health Care 2000 (Box 78)
  - Health Insurance, n.d. (Box 78)
  - House Bill 1088 (Regional Government) Newspaper Clippings 1994-1995 (Box 78)
  - House Bill 1088 Richmond Regional Government 1994 (Box 78)
  - House Bill 1088 Senate Version 1995 (Box 78)
  - House Bill 1088 Local Government Subcommittee 1994 (Box 78)
  - House Bill 1088 Coverage Dental HB 165, n.d. (Box 78)
  - House Bill 1294 Motor Vehicle Dealers, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Henrico County 1999 (Box 78)
  - Henrico County 2000 (Box 78)
  - Henrico County 2001 (Box 78)
  - Health Maintenance Organization Brochures 2000 (Box 78)
  - Homestead Law HB 1385, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Hugh Finn, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Hunting/Fishing License 2000 (Box 78)
  - Impacts of Transportation Infrastructure Investments on the Greater Richmond Region 1997 (Box 78)
  - Independent Living Problem, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Informed Consent of Abortion HB 1492 2000 (Box 78)
  - Interstate Sign Exemption 1999 (Box 78)
  - Invitations, Requests for Contributions, etc. 2000 (Box 78)
  - James River Juvenile Detention Center Water and Sewage Study 1997 (Box 78)
  - Jamestown/Yorktown 2000 (Box 78)
  - Jefferson Building, n.d. (Box 78)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, n.d. (Box 78)
  - John Tyler Community College 1999 (Box 78)
  - Joint Republican Caucus 2000 (Box 78)
  - Judgeships 2000, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - Judges-The Honorable Stephen H. Martin (Senator), n.d. (Box 78)
  - Judicial Ethics Advisory Committee, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Judicial Selection Panel 2000 (Box 78)
  - Kay Patrick vs. Car Tax Caroline County 2000 (Box 78)
  - Kyoto Protocol, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Leadership Council: Richmond Hill 2000 (Box 78)
  - Legal Services/Indigent SB 760, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Legislation 1999 (Box 78)
  - Legislative Services 2000 (Box 78)
  - Liability Insurance 1999 (Box 78)
  - List of Supporters for HB 1088, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Lobbyists 2000 (Box 78)
  - Local Government, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - Local Phone Access, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Local Source Revenue Profile of Virginia's Counties and Cities FY 89-94 1996 (Box 78)
  - Manufactured Housing 1999 (Box 78)
  - Martin Luther King Day, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Memos Jeff Gore 2000 (Box 78)
  - Metropolitan Council 1995 (Box 78)
  - Midlothian Trojans Girls Basketball Champions 2000 (Box 78)
  - Midlothian Rotary Club 2000 (Box 78)
  - Midwifery, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Midwifery SB 657, n.d. (Box 78)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings for HB 1088 1994 (Box 78)
  - Moment of Silence in Public Schools SB 209, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Monetary Contributions, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Morbid Obesity, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Motor Vehicles, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Multiple Issues, n.d. (Box 79)
  - New Judges for, 2000 (Box 79)
  - News Articles: Regionalism, n.d. (Box 79)
  - News Clippings 1999 (Box 79)
  - News Clippings 2000, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Non Profits 1999 (Box 79)
  - Notary Applications, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Notary Applications 2000 (Box 79)
  - NRA-SB 80 and SB 81 2000 (Box 79)
  - Nurse Practitioners, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Open access 1999 (Box 79)
  - Ostrich/Emu 1996 (Box 79)
  - Parental Rights Amendment 1999 (Box 79)
  - Other Regional Bills 19994 (Box 79)
  - Powhatan, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Powhatan 2000 (Box 79)
  - Powhatan Lady's Ramp Fall, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Powhatan: Legislative Program, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Planning District Commissions, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Planning District Commissions, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Portland, Oregon Metro, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Poultry Waste, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Presidential Primary SB 1287 1999 (Box 79)
  - Problem People 2000 (Box 79)
  - Propane Gas Legislation 2000 (Box 79)
  - Public Hearing Notes Info 1994 (Box 79)
  - Public Hearing Materials, Passage of HB 1088 (72-25) 1994 (Box 79)
  - Public Affairs Membership 1999 (Box 79)
  - Public Transportation Budget Amendment, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Questionnaires and Surveys, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Recommendations 2000, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Recordation Taxes SB 586, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Red Cross, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Red Cross 2000 (Box 79)
  - Redistricting, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Regional Authority Letters of Support 1997 (Box 79)
  - Regional Planning District Profile 1993 (Box 79)
  - Regional Services Study Proposal 1995-1996 (Box 79)
  - Regional States and Info. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Regional Transportation Advocacy Board 1998 (Box 79)
  - Republican Committees, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Republican Party of Virginia 2000 (Box 79)
  - Regional Freedom SB 448, n.d. (Box 79)
  - Report to the Business Community and Government by the Transportation Study Task Force of The Greater Richmond Chamber of Commerce 1996 (Box 79)
  - Research 1999 (Box 79)
  - Resumes 2000 (Box 79)
  - Rev. Russ Davis vs. Corrections 2000 (Box 79)
  - Richmond International Airport 1999 (Box 80)
  - Richmond Combined Sewer Overflow (CSO) 1999 (Box 80)
  - Richmond Center Expansion Study 1997 (Box 80)
  - Richmond City, n.d. (Box 80)
  - Richmond, City of 1999 (Box 80)
  - Richmond, City of Mainstreet Station 2000 (Box 80)
  - Richmond Legislative Program 2000 (Box 80)
  - Richmond Metro, n.d. (Box 80)
  - Richmond Metropolitan Authority (RMA), n.d. (Box 80)
  - Richmond Metropolitan Authority Tolls, n.d. (Box 80)
  - Richmond Metropolitan Statistical Area Improvement Plan 2000 (Box 80)
  - Right to Farm Court Case, n.d. (Box 80)
  - Route 288 1995 (Box 80)
  - Route 288 1996 (Box 80)
  - Route 288 James River Parkway Plans Maps 1995 (Box 80)
  - Route 288 January-May 1995-1996 (Box 80)
  - Sales Tax on Food 1999 (Box 80)
  - Sales Tax-SB 1064 1999 (Box 80)
  - SB33 Transportation 2000 (Box 80)
  - Seat Belts-SB 696 Pickup Trucks-SB 751, n.d. (Box 80)
  - Senate 2000 (Box 80)
  - Senate Clerks Office 1999 (Box 80)
  - Senate Clerks Office 2000 (Box 80)
  - Senate Clerk Susan Clark Schaar, n.d. (Box 80)
  - Senate Finance, n.d. (Box 80)
  - Senior Center of Richmond 2000 (Box 80)
  - Senate Republicans 2000 (Box 80)
  - Session 1999 (Box 80)
  - Smart Tag 1999 (Box 80)
  - SJR 61 Regional Study Correspondence 1995 (Box 80)
  - SJR Regionalism Shared Decision Making 1995 (Box 80)
  - SJR 61 Regional Studies Reports 1995 (Box 80)
  - Sjr 118 Electronic Utility, n.d. (Box 80)
  - SJR 118 Restructuring Electric Utilities, n.d. (Box 81)
  - SJR 128 Regional Incentives, n.d. (Box 81)
  - SJR 383 1995 (Box 81)
  - SJR 383 Regional 1997 (Box 81)
  - Social Events 2000 (Box 81)
  - Sodomy HB 718, n.d. (Box 81)
  - SOL, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Song-State of Virginia 1999 (Box 81)
  - Song Virginia, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Solid Waste Legislation 1999 (Box 81)
  - Solid Waste Regional 1994 (Box 81)
  - Sorenson Institute 2001 Class, 2000 (Box 81)
  - Southern Legislative Conference Economic Development, Transportation and Cultural Affairs Committee 2000 (Box 81)
  - Southern States COOP, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Special Events 2000 (Box 81)
  - Sprawl, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Steve Martin Congress 2000 (Box 81)
  - Standards of Learning 2000 (Box 81)
  - State Board of Elections 1999 (Box 81)
  - State Employees 2000 (Box 81)
  - State of the Commonwealth Address Governor Gillmore 2000 (Box 81)
  - State Song, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Strategic Review of Selected Regionalization Alternatives for the Greater Richmond Area 1997 (Box 81)
  - Students 2000 (Box 81)
  - Supreme Court, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Survey of Service Arrangements in MSA 1995 (Box 81)
  - Sympathy Condolences, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Tax Exempt Status Ronald McDonald House 2000 (Box 81)
  - Teen Drivers, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Telephone Preference Service, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Temporary Assistance for Needy Family (TANF) 2000 (Box 81)
  - Thank You, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Thank You 2000 (Box 81)
  - Thank You (From Others) 2000 (Box 81)
  - Thank You: Recommending Judicial Candidates, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Transient Occupancy Tax 1998 (Box 81)
  - Transportation, 2 folders (Box 81)
  - Transportation 2000 (Box 81)
  - Transportation Legislation 2000 (Box 81)
  - Transportation-Regional 1994 (Box 81)
  - Truck Ramp Speeds Tuition Assistance Grant (TAG), n.d. (Box 81)
  - Turks vs. Armenians HJ 298, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Unclaimed Property, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Unemployment Benefits 2000 (Box 81)
  - Uniform Computer Transactions Act, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Uniform Statewide Building Code/Farm Buildings, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Urban Partnership 1994 (Box 81)
  - Veto, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Virginia Advanced Shipbuilding and Carrier Integration center 2000 (Box 82)
  - Virginia Agribusiness 1999 (Box 82)
  - Virginia Beach: Beach Ownership 1999 (Box 82)
  - Virginia Business Council 1999 (Box 82)
  - Virginia Educational Opportunity Act, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Virginia (Dominion) Power Outrage Concerns, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Virginia Department of Transportation: Bryan Park 1999 (Box 82)
  - Virginia Department of Transportation: Roads, Traffic Disputes, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Virginia Department of Transportation: Towers, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Virginia Department of Transportation: Traffic Studies 1999 (Box 82)
  - Virginia farm Bureau, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Virginia Newspapers 1999 (Box 82)
  - VCU Regionalism: Next Step 11/1/95 (Box 82)
  - Virginia Natural Resources Policy Act, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Virginia Retirement System, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Virginia Retirement System (VRS) Optional; Ordinances, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence 2000-2001 (Box 82)
  - Wastewater-Regional, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Wetlands, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Wetlands 2000 (Box 82)
  - Wetlands Pollard, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Wetlands Plants 2000 (Box 82)
  - Workers Compensation Commission, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Zoning Ordinances HB 1456, n.d. (Box 82)
  - Zocco 1998 (Box 82)
  - Correspondence: January 1997 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence: February 1997 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence: March 1997 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence: April 1997 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence: May 1997 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence: June 1997 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence: July 1997 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence: August 1997 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence: September 1997 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence: October 1997 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence: November 1997 (Box 84)
  - Correspondence: December 1997 (Box 84)
  - Correspondence: January 1998 (Box 84)
  - Correspondence: February 1998 (Box 84)
  - Correspondence: March 1998 (Box 84)
  - Correspondence: April 1998 (Box 84)
  - Correspondence: May 1998 (Box 84)
  - Correspondence: June 1998 (Box 84)
  - Correspondence: July 1998 (Box 84)
  - Correspondence: August 1998 (Box 84)
  - Correspondence: September 1998 (Box 85)
  - Correspondence: October 1998 (Box 85)
  - Correspondence: November 1998 (Box 85)
  - Correspondence: December 1998 (Box 85)
  - Correspondence: Against HB 1088 1994 (Box 85)
  - Correspondence: Calls, Walk-ins-Veto Session 1998 (Box 85)
  - Correspondence: General 2000, 2 folders (Box 85)
  - Correspondence: Personal 2000 (Box 85)
  - Correspondence: Regionalism-Studies Articles 1994-1995 (Box 85)
  - Correspondence: Responses to Constituents, n.d. (Box 86)
  - Correspondence: Responses to Constituents 2000 (Box 86)
  - Correspondence: Senators and Delegates, n.d. (Box 86)
  - Correspondence: Support for SB 1088 1994, 2 folders (Box 86)